export const questionDatas = [
  // React Quiz Questions
  {
    category: "React",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "	Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance? ",
        options: ["Virtual DOM", "Origin DOM", "Both", "None of the above"],
        answer: "Virtual DOM",
      },
      {
        question: "	What is ReactJS?",
        options: [
          "Server-side framework",
          "user interface framework",
          "both a and b",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "user interface framework",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
        options: ["Render with arguments", "setState", "PropTypes", "props"],
        answer: "props",
      },
      {
        question: "Who created React.js?",
        options: ["Jordan Mike", "Jordan Walke", "Tim lee", "Jordan Lee"],
        answer: "Jordan Walke",
      },
      {
        question: "In which language is React.js written?",
        options: ["Python", "Javascript", "Java", "PHP"],
        answer: "Javascript",
      },
    ],
  },

  //Javascript category questions
  {
    category: "Javascript",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript? ",
        options: ["var", "let", "Both", "None of the above"],
        answer: "Both",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
        options: [
          "getElementById()",
          "getElementsByClassName()",
          "both a and b",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "both a and b",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
        options: [
          "Throws an error",
          "Ignores the statements",
          "Gives a warning",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "Ignores the statements",
      },
      {
        question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        options: ["const", "varlet", "constants"],
        answer: "const",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
        options: ["in", "is in", "exists", "lies"],
        answer: "in",
      },
    ],
  },

  //Java category questions
  {
    category: "Java",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Number of primitive data types in Java are?",
        options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        answer: "8",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the size of float and double in java?",
        options: ["32 and 64", "32 and 32", "64 and 64", "64 and 32"],
        answer: "32 and 64",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Automatic type conversion is possible in which of the possible cases?",
        options: ["Byte to int", "int to long", "long to int", "short to int"],
        answer: "int to long",
      },
      {
        question:
          "When an array is passed to a method, what does the method receive?",
        options: [
          "The reference of the array",
          "a copy of the array",
          "Length of the array",
          "Copy of first element",
        ],
        answer: "The reference of the array",
      },
      {
        question: "Arrays in java are-",
        options: [
          "object references",
          "objects",
          "primitive data types",
          "None",
        ],
        answer: "objects",
      },
    ],
  },
];
